Now you have learned how it works.
Are you thinking — does it work for me?
OxTube has been tested extensively in several university laboratories.
We still test OxTube — and receive amazing results.
Here is one test run at a university laboratory for Pure Finland.
Our client wanted to know whether OxTube would remove iron from raw water with low pH and no oxygen.
The water goes through a sand filter, where the precipitated iron stays.
Clear water flows into a small tank under the sand filter.
The result is here — guess which sample went through OxTube and the sand filter, and which one didn't.
So you are thinking: yes, it works in that case — but how about me and my case?
If we want to test OxTube with your water, we can do it very easily. Contact me.
I will come with my testing kit, and we can run water through your system.
Then you take the samples to your local laboratory — and check how much has been removed.